Dear World in Conflict fans,

Sadly, all great things must come to an end and this is true even for World in Conflict. It is with sadness that we now inform you that all online services for World in Conflict will be shut-down as of October 6th 2015. It was a very difficult decision to make but for several reasons it is not possible to keep the servers online anymore. This includes Massgate, the game severs and the forums, which means it will only be possible to play campaign and LAN games after that.

Your enjoyment of our games have always been what matters most to us. We are forever grateful for the dedication and love you have shown over the eight years since release. While this marks the end of this World in Conflict saga you should know we are working hard on other titles we hope you will come to enjoy just as much. We also want you to know that World in Conflict has a very special place in our heart and while there currently are no plans for a sequel, you never know what the future might hold!

If you have any questions regarding the shut-down, please reach out to the Customer Support team at support.ubi.com.

In closing – we at Massive thank you for your support and the love you have shown. Don’t be surprised if you see some of us joining you on the battlefield during these last weeks of World in Conflict!

// Massive Entertainment 